Party of Five Collection
Party of Five Collection
1994-2000
Syracuse University Special Collections Research Center
13 linear ft.
Scripts and production notes for the television series Party of Five
2534131
Biographical History
Party of Five was an American television series produced by Columbia Pictures Television, High Productions and Keyser/Lippman Productions and distributed by Columbia TriStar Domestic Television and the FOX Network. It premiered on FOX on September 12, 1994 and ran for six seasons until May 3, 2000. The show, a drama aimed at the teenage market and set in San Francisco, centered on five siblings living on their own after their parents were killed in an auto accident. Several cast members including Jennifer Love Hewitt and Neve Campbell went on to careers in Hollywood during and after the series. Matthew Fox went on to star in the 2004 ABC primetime hit drama Lost, while Scott Wolf later co-starred in Everwood and The Nine. The show spawned a spinoff titled Time of Your Life, which starred Jennifer Love Hewitt's character Sarah Reeves relocated to New York City.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Party of Five Collection is divided into two series. Scripts contains scripts for episodes from all six seasons of the show. Production notes consists of an assortment of material, including budgets, correspondence, memos, personnel files, photographs, promotional and publicity material, and schedules.
Arrangement of the Collection
Both Scripts and Production notes are subdivided by season and within that are listed in order by episode number, with air date. Production dates are given in parenthesis ( ).
Related Material
has a number of television-related collections. Please refer to for a complete listing
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Popular culture; Party of five (television series); Popular culture -- United States.; Television -- Production and direction.; Television series -- United States.; Budgets.; Correspondence.; Memorabilia.; Memorandums.; Photographs.; Promotional materials.; Scripts (documents); Television producers and directors.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Scripts
  - Season 1
    - Episode 1 (16721) Homework (production dates: 7/20/94 - 7/28/94), 9/19/1994; includes personal info (Box 1)
    - Episode 2 (16722) Good Sports (production dates: 7/29/94 - 8/8/94), 9/26/1994; includes personal info (Box 1)
    - Episode 3 (16723) Worth Waiting For (production dates: 8/9/94 - 8/17/94), 10/3/1994 (Box 1)
    - Episode 4 (16724) All's Fair (production dates: 8/18/94 - 8/26/94), 10/10/1994 (Box 1)
    - Episode 5 (16725) Fathers and Sons (production dates: 8/31/94 - 9/9/94), 10/17/1994 (Box 1)
    - Episode 6 (16726) Much Ado (production dates: 9/12/94 - 9/20/94), 10/24/1994 (Box 1)
    - Episode 7 (16727) Kiss Me Kate (production dates: 9/20/94 - 9/29/94), 11/2/1994 (Box 1)
    - Episode 8 (16728) Something Out of Nothing (production dates: 9/30/94 - 10/10/94), 11/7/1994 (Box 1)
    - Episode 9 (16729) Thanksgiving (production dates: 10/11/94 - 10/19/94), 11/21/1994; includes personal info (Box 1)
    - Episode 10 (16730) Private Lives (production dates: 10/20/94 - 10/28/94), 11/14/1994 (Box 1)
    - Episode 11 (16731) Games People Play (production dates: 10/31/94 - 11/8/94), 11/28/1994 (Box 1)
    - Episode 12 (16732) Grown Ups (production dates: 11/9/94 - 11/17/94), 12/12/1994 (Box 1)
    - Episode 13 (16733) Not Fade Away (production dates: 11/18/94 - 1 1 /30/94), 1/4/1995 (Box 2)
    - Episode 14 (16734) It's Not Easy Being Green (production dates: 12/1/94 - 12/9/94), 1/11/1995 (Box 2)
    - Episode 15 (16735) After Shocks (production dates: 12/8/94 - 12/20/94), 1/18/1995 (Box 2)
    - Episode 16 (16736) In Loco Parentis (production dates: 1/3/95 - 1/12/95), 2/1/1995; revised pages only, no script (Box 2)
    - Episode 17 (16737) Who Cares? (production dates: 1/13/95 - 1/23/95), 2/15/1995 (Box 2)
    - Episode 18 (16738) Brother's Keeper (production dates: 1/24/95 - 2/1/95), 2/22/1995 (Box 2)
    - Episode 19 (16739) Trouble with Charlie (production dates: 2/2/95 - 2/10/95), 3/1/1995; includes personal info (Box 2)
    - Episode 20 (16740) All Nighters (production dates: 2/13/95 - 2/22/95), 3/8/1995; includes personal info (Box 2)
    - Episode 21 (16741) Ides of March (production dates: 2/23/95 - 3/3/95), 3/15/1995 (Box 2)
  - Season 2
    - Episode 1 (161821) Ready or Not (production dates: 7/17/95 - 7/25/95), 9/27/1995 (Box 3)
    - Episode 2 (161822) Falsies (production dates: 7/26/95 - 8/3/95), 10/4/1995 (Box 3)
    - Episode 3 (161823) Dearly Beloved (production dates: 8/4/95 - 8/15/95), 10/18/1995 (Box 3)
    - Episode 4 (161824) Have No Fear (production dates: 8/15/95 - 8/24/95), 10/25/1995 (Box 3)
    - Episode 5 (161825) Change Partners & Dance (production dates: 8/25/95 - 9/6/95), 11/1/1995; includes personal info (Box 3)
    - Episode 6 (161826) Analogies (production dates: 9/9/95 - 9/15/95), 11/8/1995; includes personal info (Box 3)
    - Episode 7 (161827) Where There's Smoke (production dates: 9/18/95 - 9/26/95), 11/15/1995 (Box 3)
    - Episode 8 (161828) The Best Laid Plans (production dates: 9/27/95 - 10/19/95), 11/22/1995 (Box 3)
    - Episode 9 (161829) The Wedding (production dates: 10/5/95 - 10/13/95), 12/13/1995 (Box 3)
    - Episode 10 (161830) Grand Delusions (production dates: 10/16/95 - 10/25/95), 12/20/1995; 2nd copy of script (Box 3)
    - Episode 11 (161831) Unfair Advantage (production dates: 10/26/95 - 11/3/95), 1/3/1996 (Box 3)
    - Episode 12 (161832) Hold on Tight (production dates: 11/6/95 - 11/14/95), 1/10/1996 (Box 4)
    - Episode 13 (161833) Poor Substitutes (production dates: 11/15/95 - 11/27/95), 1/17/1996 (Box 4)
    - Episode 14 (161834) Strange Bedfellows (production dates: 11/28/95 - 12/6/95), 1/24/1996 (Box 4)
    - Episode 15 (161835) Benefactors (production dates: 12/7/95 - 12/15/95), 1/31/1996 (Box 4)
    - Episode 16 (161836) Comings and Goings (production dates: 1/2/96 - 1/10/96), 2/7/1996 (Box 4)
    - Episode 17 (161837) Valentines Day (production dates: 1/11/96 - 1/19/96), 2/14/1996; revised pages only, no script (Box 4)
    - Episode 18 (161838) Before and After (production dates: 1/22/96 - 1/30/96), 2/21/1996 (Box 4)
    - Episode 19 (161839) Altered States (production dates: 1 /31 /96 - 2/8/96), 2/28/1996 (Box 4)
    - Episode 20 (161840) Happily Ever After (production dates: 2/9/96 - 2/20/96), 3/20/1996 (Box 4)
    - Episode 21 (161841) Spring Breaks Part I (production dates: 2/21/96 - 2/29/96), 3/27/1996 (Box 4)
    - Episode 22 (161842) Spring Breaks Part II (production dates: 3/1/96 - 3/11/96), 3/27/1996 (Box 4)
  - Season 3
    - Episode 1 (161871) Summer Fun, Summer Not (production dates: 7/2/96-7/9/96), 8/21/1996; No script (Box 5)
    - Episode 2 (161872) Going Going Gone (production dates: 6/24/96 - 7/1/96), 8/28/1996; No script, personal info (Box 5)
    - Episode 3 (161873) Short Cuts (production dates: 7/10/96 - 7/18/96), 9/4/1996 (Box 5)
    - Episode 4 (161874) Deal With It (production dates: 7/18/96 - 8/2/96), 9/11/1996; no script (Box 5)
    - Episode 5 (161875) Mixed Signals (production dates: 8/5/96 - 8/12/96), 9/18/1996 (Box 5)
    - Episode 6 (161876) Going Home (production dates: `8/13/96 - 8/21/96), 9/25/1996 (Box 5)
    - Episode 7 (161877) Personal Demons (production dates: 8/22/96 - 8/30/96), 10/30/1996; includes personal info (Box 5)
    - Episode 8 (161878) Not So Fast (production dates: 9/3/96 - 9/11/96), 11/6/1996 (Box 5)
    - Episode 9 (161879) Gimme Shelter (production dates: 9/12/96 - 9/20/96), 11/13/1996 (Box 5)
    - Episode 10 (161880) Close to You (production dates: to You), 11/20/1996 (Box 5)
    - Episode 11 (161881) I Do (production dates: 10/2/96 - 10/10/96), 11/27/1996; includes personal info (Box 5)
    - Episode 12 (161882) Desparate Measures (production dates: 10/11/96 - 10/21/96), 12/11/1996 (Box 5)
    - Episode 13 (161883) Christmas (production dates: 10/22/96 - 10/30/96), 12/18/1996 (Box 5)
    - Episode 14 (161884) Life's Too Short (production dates: 10/31/96 - 11/8/96), 1/8/1997 (Box 5)
    - Episode 15 (161885) Significant Others (production dates: 11/11/96 -11/19/96), 1/15/1997; revised pages only, no script (Box 6)
    - Episode 16 (161886) I Declare (production dates: 11/20/96 - 12/2/96), 1/22/1997 (Box 6)
    - Episode 17 (161887) Misery Loves Company (production dates: 12/3/96 - 12/11/96), 1/29/1997 (Box 6)
    - Episode 18 (161888) MYOB (production dates: 12/12/96 - 12/20/96), 2/5/1997 (Box 6)
    - Episode 19 (161889) Point of No Return (production dates: 1/2/97 - 1/10/97), 2/12/1997 (Box 6)
    - Episode 20 (161890) Intervention (production dates: 1/13/97 - 1/21/97), 2/19/1997 (Box 6)
    - Episode 21 (161891) Hitting Bottom (production dates: 1/22/97 - 1/30/97), 2/26/1997 (Box 6)
    - Episode 22 (161892) Leap of Faith (production dates: 1/31/97 - 2/10/97), 3/5/1997; no script (Box 6)
    - Episode 23 (161893) Promises Promises (production dates: 2/11/97 - 2/20/97), 5/19/1997 (Box 6)
    - Episode 24 (161894) A Little Faith (production dates: 2/21/97 - 3/3/97), 5/26/1997 (Box 6)
    - Episode 25 (161895) You Win Some, You Lose Some (production dates: 3/4/97 - 3/13/97), 4/2/1997 (Box 6)
  - Season 4
    - Episode 1 (160911) What a Drag (production dates: 7/21/97 - 7/29/97), 9/17/1997; 2nd copy of script (Box 7)
    - Episode 2 (160912) Past Imperfect (production dates: 7/30/97 - 8/7/97), 9/24/1997; includes personal info (Box 7)
    - Episode 3 (160913) Hadicaps (production dates: 8/8/97 - 8/18/97), 10/1/1997; includes personal info (Box 7)
    - Episode 4 (160914) Zap (production dates: 8/18/97 - 8/27/97), 10/15/1997 (Box 7)
    - Episode 5 (160915) Fight or Flight (production dates: 8/28/97 - 9/5/97), 10/22/1997; includes personal info (Box 7)
    - Episode 6 (160916) Immediate Family (production dates: 9/8/97 - 9/15/97), 10/29/1997; revised pages only, no script (Box 7)
    - Episode 7 (160917) Positive Attitude (production dates: 9/16/97 - 9/30/97), 11/5/1997; revised pages only, no script (Box 7)
    - Episode 8 (160918) Sickness,Health / Richer,Poorer (production dates: 9/26/97 - 10/9/97), 11/12/1997 (Box 7)
    - Episode 9 (160919) Truth Be Told (production dates: 10/10/97 - 10/17/97), 11/19/1997 (Box 7)
    - Episode 10 (160920) Adjustments (production dates: 10/20/97 - 10/28/97), 12/3/1997 (Box 7)
    - Episode 11 (160921) S'wunnerful Life (production dates: 10/29/97 - 11/6/97), 12/12/1997 (Box 7)
    - Episode 12 (160922) Empty Shoes (production dates: 11/7/97 - 11/17/97), 1/7/1998 (Box 7)
    - Episode 13 (160923) Parent Trap (production dates: 11/18/97 - 11/26/97), 1/14/1998 (Box 7)
    - Episode 14 (160924) Of Human Bonding (production dates: 12/1/97 - 12/9/97), 1/21/1998; 2nd copy of script (Box 7)
    - Episode 15 (160925) Here and Now (production dates: 12/10/97 - 12/18/97), 1/28/1998 (Box 7)
    - Episode 16 (160926) I Give Up (production dates: 1/5/98 - 1/13/98), 2/4/1998 (Box 7)
    - Episode 17 (160927) Of Sound Mind and Body (production dates: 1/14/98 - 1/23/98), 2/11/1998 (Box 8)
    - Episode 18 (160928) True or False (production dates: 1/26/98 - 2/3/98), 2/25/1998; includes personal info (Box 8)
    - Episode 19 (160929) Go Away (production dates: 2/4/98 - 2/12/98), 3/4/1998 (Box 8)
    - Episode 20 (160930) Square One (production dates: 2/9/98 - 2/25/98), 4/22/1998 (Box 8)
    - Episode 21 (160931) Free and Clear (production dates: 2124/98 - 3/5/98), 4/22/1998 (Box 8)
    - Episode 22 (160932) Opposites Distract (production dates: 3/6/98 - 3/16/98), 4/29/1998 (Box 8)
    - Episode 23 (160933) Fools Rush In (production dates: 3/17/98 - 3/25/98), 5/6/1998; not a complete script (Box 8)
    - Episode 24 (160934) Fools Rush Out, 5/13/1998; NO FILE OR SCRIPT (Box 8)
  - Season 5
    - Episode 1 (171011) Moving On (production dates: 7/22/98 - 8/24/98), 9/16/1998 (Box 9)
    - Episode 2 (171012) Separation Anxiety (production dates: 7/30/98 - 8/25/98), 9/23/1998; includes personal info (Box 9)
    - Episode 3 (171013) Naming Names (production dates: 8/7/98 - 8/14/98), 9/30/1998; includes personal info (Box 9)
    - Episode 4 (171014) Midsemester Night Dream (production dates: 10/28/98), 10/28/1998 (Box 9)
    - Episode 5 (171015) The Baby (production dates: 11/4/98), 11/4/1998 (Box 9)
    - Episode 6 (171016) Forgive And/Or Forget (production dates: 9/11/98 - 9/22/98), 11/11/1998 (Box 9)
    - Episode 7 (171017) Tender Age (production dates: 9/23/98 - 10/2/98), 11/18/1998 (Box 9)
    - Episode 8 (171018) Love and War (production dates: 10/2/98 - 10/13/98), 12/2/1998 (Box 9)
    - Episode 9 (171019) Gifts (production dates: 10/13/98 - 10/21/98), 12/9/1998 (Box 9)
    - Episode 10 (171020) One Christmas to Go (production dates: 1112/98 - 11/10/98), 12/16/1998 (Box 9)
    - Episode 11 (171021) Rings of Saturn (production dates: 11/2/98 - 11/10/98), 1/13/1999 (Box 9)
    - Episode 12 (171022) Witness for the Persecution (production dates: 11/10/98 - 11/19/98), 1/20/1999; includes personal info (Box 9)
    - Episode 13 (171023) Fillmore Street (production dates: 11/20/98 - 12/2/98), 1/27/1999 (Box 9)
    - Episode 14 (171024) Stand By Me (production dates: 12/1/98 -12/11/98), 2/3/1999; revised pages only - no script (Box 9)
    - Episode 15 (171025) Whatever Works (production dates: 12/14/98 - 12/22/98), 2/10/1999 (Box 9)
    - Episode 16 (171026) Party of Freud (production dates: 1/4/99 - 1/12/99), 2/17/1999 (Box 9)
    - Episode 17 (171027) fam-i-ly (production dates: 1/13/99 - 1/22/99), 3/3/1999 (Box 9)
    - Episode 18 (171028) Driven to Extremes (production dates: 1/25/99 - 2/3/99), 3/10/1999 (Box 9)
    - Episode 19 (171029) Judgement Day (production dates: 2/4/99 - 2/18/99), 3/17/1999 (Box 9)
    - Episode 20 (171030) The Wish (production dates: 2/19/99 - 2/25/99), 4/14/1999 (Box 10)
    - Episode 21 (171031) Get Back (production dates: 2/26/99 - 3/8/99), 4/21/1999 (Box 10)
    - Episode 22 (171032) Fragile (production dates: 2/17/99 - 3/17/99), 4/28/1999; includes extra info on REM (Box 10)
    - Episode 23 (171033) I'll Show You Mine (production dates: 3/17/99 - 3/25/99), 5/5/1999; also has title "The Tests" (Box 10)
    - Episode 24 (171034) Haunted (production dates: 3/26/99 - 4/6/99), 5/12/1999 (Box 10)
    - Episode 25 (171035) Otherwise Engaged (production dates: 4/7/99 - 4/15/99), 5/19/1999 (Box 10)
  - Season 6
    - Episode 1 (170611) Don't Let Go (production dates: 7/21/99 - 7/29/99), 10/5/1999 (Box 11)
    - Episode 2 (170612) Naked (production dates: 7/29/99 - 8/9/99), 10/12/1999 (Box 11)
    - Episode 3 (170613) Bye, Bye Love (production dates: 8/10/99 - 8/18/99), 10/19/1999 (Box 11)
    - Episode 4 (170614) Wrestling Demons (production dates: 8/19/99 - 8/27/99), 10/26/1999 (Box 11)
    - Episode 5 (170615) The Shortest Distance (production dates: 8/30/99 - 9/8/99), 11/2/1999 (Box 11)
    - Episode 6 (170616) Too Close (production dates: 9/8/99 - 9/16/99), 11/9/1999 (Box 11)
    - Episode 7 (170617) We Gather Together (production dates: 9/16/99 - 9/24/99), 11/16/1999 (Box 11)
    - Episode 8 (170618) Wrong Turns (production dates: 9/24/99 - 10/4/99), 11/30/1999 (Box 11)
    - Episode 9 (170619) Ties That Bind (production dates: 10/11/99 - 10/19/99), 12/7/1999 (Box 11)
    - Episode 10 (170620) The Moment (production dates: 10/19/99 - 10/27/99), 1/11/2000; "Dog Day After New Year" (Box 11)
    - Episode 11 (170621) Fear & Loathing (production dates: 10/28/99 - 11/8/99), 1/18/2000 (Box 11)
    - Episode 12 (170622) Bad Behavior (production dates: 11/4/99 - 11/16/99), 1/25/2000 (Box 11)
    - Episode 13 (170623) Declaration of Co-Dependence (production dates: 11/17/99 - 11/29/99), 2/1/2000 (Box 11)
    - Episode 14 (170624) One for the Road (production dates: 11/30/99 - 12/8/99), 2/8/2000 (Box 11)
    - Episode 15 (170625) What If... (production dates: 12/9/99 - 1/5/00), 2/22/2000 (Box 11)
    - Episode 16 (170626) Blast the Past (production dates: 1/6/00 - 1/14/00), 3/14/2000 (Box 12)
    - Episode 17 (170627) Getting There (production dates: 1/18/00 - 1/26/00), 3/21/2000 (Box 12)
    - Episode 18 (170628) Too Cool for School (production dates: 1/27/00 - 2/4/00), 4/4/2000 (Box 12)
    - Episode 19 (170629) Isn't it Romantic (production dates: 2/7/00 - 2/15/00), 4/11/2000; 2nd copy of script (Box 12)
    - Episode 20 (170630) Great Expectations (production dates: 2/16/00 - 2/25/00), 4/18/2000 (Box 12)
    - Episode 21 (170631) Taboo or not Taboo (production dates: 2/28/00 - 3/7/00), 4/19/2000 (Box 12)
    - Episode 22 (170632) Falling Forward (production dates: 3/7/00 - 3/16/00), 4/26/2000 (Box 12)
    - Episode 23 (170633) All's Well (production dates: 3/17/00 - 3/27/00), 5/3/2000 (Box 12)
    - Episode 24 (170634) That Ends Well (production dates: 3/31/00 - 4/6/00), 5/3/2000; working draft of script (Box 12)
- Production notes
  - Season 1
    - Personnel Files
      - Lorraine Hendricks (Box 13)
      - Roy Wagner (Box 13)
      - Celia Weiner (Box 13)
      - R. Russell (Rusty) Smith (Box 13)
      - Greg Orloff (Box 13)
    - Location Photos, 10 folders (Box 13)
    - Babies (Box 13)
    - Choreographers (Box 13)
    - Production Reports (Box 13)
    - Letter to Warner Adler from Ken Topolsky (Box 13)
    - Pre-Production Schedule (Box 13)
    - Worth Waiting For Script (Box 13)
    - Good Sports (Box 13)
    - One Line Schedule (Box 13)
    - List of outstanding residuals from "The Wonder Years" (Box 13)
    - Travel Paraphernalia for Ken Topolsky and Newspaper Clippings (Box 13)
    - Cover Letters (Box 13)
    - Distribution File - Notice of Sexual Harassment between two employees (Box 13)
    - Incoming Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Outgoing Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Daily Schedule (Box 13)
    - Vancouver Inventory (Box 13)
    - Air Dates - Empty Folder (Box 13)
    - Memos (Box 13)
    - Memos Outgoing (Box 13)
    - Post Schedules (Box 13)
    - Call Sheets (Box 13)
    - Production Rept. (Box 13)
    - Harassment (Box 13)
    - Clearances (Box 13)
    - Dog Agreement (Box 13)
    - Billboard 100 (Box 13)
    - Assorted Sheet Music (Box 13)
    - Music Clearance (Box 13)
    - Summaries (Box 13)
    - Memos - Music Choices (Box 13)
    - Pre-Cleared Artist Rept. - Empty Folder (Box 13)
    - Sony Artist Roster (Box 13)
    - Music Jokes (Box 13)
  - Season 2
    - Correspondence (Box 13)
      - Incoming (Box 13)
      - Outgoing (Box 13)
      - Interoffice (Box 13)
    - Party Info (Box 13)
    - Publicity General (Box 13)
    - Schedules - Production (Box 13)
    - Schedules - Post (Box 13)
    - Camera Info (Box 13)
  - Season 3
    - Correspondence - Outgoing (Box 13)
    - Post Production - Air Schedules (Box 13)
    - Post Productions - Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Post - Music Summary (Box 13)
    - Publicity - General (Box 13)
    - Schedules - Production (Box 13)
    - California Celebrations Portfolio (Box 13)
    - Sony Picture Warehouse System - Properties Inventory (Box 13)
    - San Francisco Tourist Book (Box 13)
    - Location Photos (Box 13)
  - Season 4
    - Correspondence
      - Interoffice (Box 13)
      - Outgoing (Box 13)
    - Post Production - Air Date Schedule (Box 13)
    - Post Production - Schedule (Box 13)
    - Publicity - General (Box 13)
    - Wrap - Gift Ideas (Box 13)
    - City Council Information (Box 13)
    - San Francisco - General (Box 13)
    - Budgets - San Francisco (Box 13)
    - Schedules - Production (Box 13)
  - Season 5
    - Correspondence
      - Outgoing (Box 13)
      - Incoming (Box 13)
      - Interoffice (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - Stanford University (Box 13)
    - Wrap - Gift Ideas (Box 13)
    - Wrap - Party Ideas (Box 13)
    - DGA Grievance (Box 13)
    - Crew Days Off (Box 13)
    - Episode Synopsis (Box 13)
    - MS&L Luncheon -, 5/6/99 (Box 13)
    - Ratings, 1998/99 (Box 13)
    - R.E.M. - Eps. 22 (Box 13)
    - Research (Box 13)
    - Stages Wrap, 1999 (Box 13)
    - San Francisco Board (Box 13)
    - Post Production - Air Dates Schedule (Box 13)
    - Post Production - Crew List (Box 13)
    - Post Production - Schedule (Box 13)
    - Dr. Pepper Promo (Box 13)
    - Releases (Box 13)
    - Emmy, 1999 (Box 13)
    - Red Cross Spirit Awards, 3/6/99 (Box 13)
    - Rosie O'Donnell, 2/1/99 (Box 13)
    - The Vision Awards '99 (Box 13)
    - Schedules - Season (Box 13)
    - TV Guide, April 24-30, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Season 6
    - Bailey's Girlfriend (Box 13)
    - Crew Auction (Box 13)
    - Cyrano de Bergerac - Episode 603 (Box 13)
    - Director Considerations (Box 13)
    - Finale Screening (Box 13)
    - The Flys - Eps. 15 (Box 13)
    - Brad Gelford Tour Pitch (Box 13)
    - iwin.com (Box 13)
    - NFL - 49'ers (Box 13)
    - Nursing Home Pitch (Box 13)
    - Salinger House Website (Box 13)
    - Sony Metreon (Box 13)
    - Start Dates (Box 13)
    - Yahoo Auction (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - BLOW - Jacobs (Box 13)
    - Get Carter - Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Scream 3 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Beckham (Box 13)
    - Crew List - Empty Folder (Box 13)
    - CTTV Clearance Procedures (Box 13)
    - Credits (Box 13)
    - Delivery Requirements (Box 13)
    - 99/00 Print Cross Promo Campaign (Box 13)
    - Fashion Bug Promo (Box 13)
    - Kudo's (Box 13)
    - Series Finale Press Release (Box 13)
    - Spirit Awards (Shine Awards) (Box 13)
    - TCA, 7/22/99 (Box 13)
    - The Vision Awards, 6/19/99 (Box 13)
    - Camera (Box 13)
    - Editors (Box 13)
    - Hair/Make-up - Empty Folder (Box 13)
    - Locations (Box 13)
    - Music - Empty Folder (Box 13)
    - San Francisco (Box 13)
    - SF
      - Budget (Box 13)
      - Call Sheets (Box 13)
      - Crew - Empty Folder (Box 13)
      - Packet (Box 13)
      - Production Reports (Box 13)
    - Season Schedule (Box 13)
    - Gifts - Cast Photo Negatives (Box 13)
    - Party (Box 13)
    - Budget
      - AMORT (Box 13)
      - Correspondence (Box 13)
      - Pattern (Box 13)
      - Disputed Studio Charges - Empty Folder (Box 13)
      - Prep Analysis (Box 13)
      - Summary of Picture Costs (Box 13)
      - Talent Compensation (Box 13)